<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
    <addon id="plugin.video.fenlight" name="Fen Light" provider-name="Tikipeter" version="2.0.13">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
            <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
            <license />
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/media/fenlight_icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
            <news>INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.fenlight.patched" name="Fen Light Patched" provider-name="Tikipeter" version="2.0.30">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
            <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
            <license />
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/media/fenlight_icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
            <news>[v2.0.30]:
  * Clear local Kodi bookmark rows using the real plugin:// playback URLs so erase-bookmark actions target the active movie or episode instead of relying on the old broad filename match.

[v2.0.28]:
  * Keep the smoother autoplay handoff that waits for fullscreen before closing the resolver window, reducing the flash back to the skin start screen.
  * Bridge selector playback metadata into Kodi properties so patched a4k can consume the exact selector-chosen subtitle for the active source at runtime.
  * Trim the successful pre-player settle before player.run(...) to reduce startup latency without changing retry timing.

[v2.0.26]:
  * Ship Fen Light Patched with reuse language invoker disabled by default so repo installs stop re-enabling it for setups that expect it off.

[v2.0.25]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v2.0.24]:
  * Prefer direct subtitle filename evidence over uploader comments when both are available.
  * Strip OpenSubtitles track and language suffixes before source/subtitle matching.

[v2.0.23]:
  * Bundle the subtitle selector inside the add-on instead of depending on an external dev repo path.
  * Build the autoplay retry pool from one title-level subtitle gather and local selector ranking.

INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.kodi.synctool" name="Kodi Sync Tool" version="0.2.39" provider-name="Codex">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="sync_now.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="pair_google_drive.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Sync selected Kodi data with Google Drive</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">A background service add-on for syncing selected Kodi files and folders with Google Drive using OAuth refresh tokens.</description>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>MIT</license>
            <source>https://example.invalid/service.kodi.synctool</source>
            <news>v0.2.39
- Move full release history into CHANGELOG.md so repository metadata stays compact

v0.2.38
- Add multi-category sync targets for core data, skin widgets, addon settings backups, and custom file or folder paths

Full release history is now tracked in CHANGELOG.md.</news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.a4ksubtitles" name="a4kSubtitles" version="3.23.8" provider-name="Unknown">
        <requires>
            <import addon="script.module.requests" />
            <import addon="vfs.libarchive" optional="true" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="main.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="main_service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en">a4kSubtitles - Multi-Source Subtitles Addon</summary>
            <description>
Multi-source subtitles addon optimized for Seren and a4kScrapers.
Supports: OpenSubtitles, BSPlayer, Podnadpisi.NET, SubDL, Addic7ed
        </description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <license>MIT License</license>
            <website>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</website>
            <source>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>icon.png</icon>
                <screenshot>screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
                <screenshot>screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
                <screenshot>screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
            </assets>
            <news>
[v3.23.8]:
  * Move full release history into CHANGELOG.md so repository metadata stays compact.

[v3.23.7]:
  * Relax OpenSubtitles TV episode IMDb filtering in API-mode pre-play searches so valid episode subtitle results survive to Fenlight matching.

[v3.23.6]:
  * Add targeted search pipeline logging for API-mode pre-play debugging, including raw service results and each prepare/filter stage.

Full release history is now tracked in CHANGELOG.md.
        </news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.a4ksubtitles.patched" name="a4kSubtitles Patched" version="3.23.26" provider-name="Unknown">
        <requires>
            <import addon="script.module.requests" />
            <import addon="vfs.libarchive" optional="true" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="main.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="main_service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en">a4kSubtitles Patched - Multi-Source Subtitles Addon</summary>
            <description>
Multi-source subtitles addon optimized for Seren and a4kScrapers.
Supports: OpenSubtitles, BSPlayer, Podnadpisi.NET, SubDL, Addic7ed
        </description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <license>MIT License</license>
            <website>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</website>
            <source>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>icon.png</icon>
                <screenshot>screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
                <screenshot>screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
                <screenshot>screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
            </assets>
            <news>
[v3.23.26]:
  * Bypass the persisted subtitle-results cache during API-mode searches so Fenlight pre-play subtitle gathers always use a fresh subtitle result set instead of stale runtime cache state.

[v3.23.23]:
  * Consume Fenlight's selector-provided subtitle payload at runtime, keyed to the active playback source, before falling back to a fresh runtime search.
  * Speed up selector-backed startup attachment by fast-polling during the first playback seconds and trying the forced selector subtitle before the IMDb-gated fallback search.
  * On OpenSubtitles download 401, clear cached auth state, re-login once, and retry the same candidate so stale token failures recover automatically.
  * Shift movie OpenSubtitles retrieval toward IMDb-first searches with filename-year correction fallback so bad metadata years no longer suppress valid subtitle hits.

[v3.23.21]:
  * Prevent autoplay subtitle preparation from crashing when uploader comments contain Unicode digit separators such as ².
  * Rewrite matching-stem runtime subtitle temp filenames before attach so Kodi shows a readable external subtitle name instead of collapsing to generic (External).

[v3.23.20]:
  * Migrate the Kodi settings dialog to the current schema so provider toggles and account fields no longer reset while switching categories.
  * Restore selector shadow snapshots for multi-provider runs, including paired Fenlight source snapshots and history-only runtime/manual subtitle snapshots.
  * Make manual subtitle picks attach the real downloaded file directly so Kodi shows the chosen release name instead of TempSubtitle, without the old false failed-download notice.

[v3.23.19]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v3.23.18]:
  * Add universal [AI]/[MT] badges to manual search subtitle rows so translated results are clearly marked across skins.

[v3.23.17]:
  * Prefer full OpenSubtitles release names for selector matching.
  * Keep API-mode settings overrides compatible with Kodi's read-only Addon object.
  * Refresh cached rows missing translation flags before selector ranking.

[v3.23.13]:
  * Fix comment-fallback ranking crash in final subtitle selection.

[v3.23.12]:
  * Use OpenSubtitles uploader comments as a fallback-only compatibility signal after direct filename matching.

[v3.23.11]:
  * Demote AI and machine-translated subtitle results during final ranking so they only win as fallback.

[v3.23.10]:
  * Move full release history into CHANGELOG.md so repository metadata stays compact.

[v3.23.9]:
  * Fix OpenSubtitles download retries and cleanup after failed downloads.
  * Improve subtitle ranking for prerelease and release-family mismatches.
  * Add resilient OpenSubtitles movie fallback search when year metadata is wrong.
  * Show a notification when an AI or machine translated subtitle is selected.

Full release history is now tracked in CHANGELOG.md.
        </news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="repository.dutchtechtestrepo" name="DutchTechTestRepo" provider-name="DutchTech" version="1.0.5">
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="DutchTechTestRepo">
            <dir>
                <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TechXXX/DutchTechTestRepo/main/addons.xml</info>
                <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TechXXX/DutchTechTestRepo/main/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
                <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TechXXX/DutchTechTestRepo/main/zips/</datadir>
            </dir>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>Testing repository for DutchTech Kodi add-ons.</summary>
            <description>Install this testing repository to receive DutchTech Kodi test add-on updates from a GitHub Pages-hosted source.</description>
            <disclaimer />
            <platform>all</platform>
            <assets>
                <icon>icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
</addons>
